

Javascript

• React

• Git

Framework

Version Control

Skills

Technologies

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- SASS
- Bootstrap

Database

- MongoDB
- MySQL

Others

- Agile Development
- Project Management

Certifications

German Language Certificate - B1 French Language Certificate - A2

Languages

English: Fluent (C1)

German: Intermediate (B1)

French (A2)

Punjabi (Mother Tongue)

Contact

Email

dearkamalpreet@gmail.com

<u>Pho</u>ne

+49 176 22336440

Address

GleiwitzerStraße 5, Kaarst Germany







Kamalpreet Kaur

Fullstack Web Developer

Fullstack Web Developer with 5+ years of experience as teacher & examination coordinator who recently graduated from a 1-year intensive training in Fullstack Web Development (MERN Stack). As a Web Developer, my objective is to make a positive impact on clients, co-workers and the Internet using my skills and experience to design compelling and attractive websites.

Education

2022 - 2023

Fullstack Web Development DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH, Düsseldorf

- Accomplishing a one year full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing many small and one big final project to practice programming skills
- Taking German lessons as a part of the course with a certificate in Level B2

2014 - 2015

Bachelor of Education

Maharishi Dayanand University, Rohtak India

- secured 71% Marks.

2009 - 2011

Masters of Science (Physics)

Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar India

- secured 67% Marks.

2006 - 2009

Bachelor of Science (Physics)

Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar India

- secured 68% Marks.

Crew Member

Experience

O 2019 - 2020

McDonald's Düsseldorf

- Maintained smooth customer service and satisfaction in a stressful environment.
- Gained important soft-skills such as team-orientation, quick-thinking and flexibility in the German job market.

O 2016 - 2019 Mathematics Teacher

Sapphire International School, Noida India

- Designed and implemented lesson plans incorporated Algebra, Geometry & probability.
- Created interactive learning environment by using Smart board.
- Preparing academic planner and course outline or all subjects.
- Participating in workshops for professional developments.

Key Achievements: I have organised the Sports event with the help of Sports staff and was also an examination incharge for primary wing.

O 2011 - 2013 Mathematics and Science Teacher

Divine Will Public School, Punjab India